<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>importance on Napolitano-Tseng</title><link>https://www.napolitano-tseng.com/tags/importance/</link><description>Recent content in importance on Napolitano-Tseng</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.napolitano-tseng.com/tags/importance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Importance of Empirical Analysis in Market Research</title><link>https://www.napolitano-tseng.com/blog/empirical/empirical/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.napolitano-tseng.com/blog/empirical/empirical/</guid><description>Empirical Analysis We focus on acquiring quality empirical data to prepare every report that we produce. Qualitative data and quantitive data must be verfied prior to including them in any project. Our data driven approach guarantees that our work is to the greatest extent possible free of bias and methodological errors.</description></item><item><title>The Importance of Rigor in Market Research</title><link>https://www.napolitano-tseng.com/blog/rigor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.napolitano-tseng.com/blog/rigor/</guid><description>Rigor Market Research reports are often manipulated to appeal to the bias of consumers. Rounding errors, small alphas, and closed source reports do not provide the rigor that analysis consumer deserve.
In our experience, technical reports detailing accurate results may not appeal to sales teams, founders, and executives that must justify their product to their board. We find that papers prepared according to the highest standards defined in the academic literature may not yield the results that consumers may expect.</description></item><item><title>The Importance of Rigor in Market Research</title><link>https://www.napolitano-tseng.com/blog/rigor/rigor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.napolitano-tseng.com/blog/rigor/rigor/</guid><description>Rigor Market Research reports are often manipulated to appeal to the bias of consumers. Rounding errors, small alphas, and closed source reports do not provide the rigor that analysis consumer deserve.
In our experience, technical reports detailing accurate results may not appeal to sales teams, founders, and executives that must justify their product to their board. We find that papers prepared according to the highest standards defined in the academic literature may not yield the results that consumers may expect.</description></item><item><title>The Importance of Transparency in Market Research</title><link>https://www.napolitano-tseng.com/blog/transparency/transparency/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.napolitano-tseng.com/blog/transparency/transparency/</guid><description>Transparency Black box models are the norm in the research industry. Some companies believe that their algorithms and pipelines are a product that must protected from the peering eyes of competitors. We take another aproach.
Napolitano-Tseng believes models should be documented and published in order for our clients to ensure that the work provided to them is produced according to the highest industry standards. When we are chosen to create reports, we include notebooks that document every part of our procedures to our customers.</description></item></channel></rss>