<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Napolitano-Tseng</title><link>https://justin-napolitano.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Napolitano-Tseng</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://justin-napolitano.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud Infrastructure Development and Management</title><link>https://justin-napolitano.github.io/products/cloud-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 12:33:45 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://justin-napolitano.github.io/products/cloud-infrastructure/</guid><description>Cloud Infrastructure Development Cloud native applications work best in orchestrated environments deployed to a cloud service. We deploy services that minimize downtime and scale automatically according to demand.</description></item><item><title>CRM Development</title><link>https://justin-napolitano.github.io/products/crm/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 12:33:45 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://justin-napolitano.github.io/products/crm/</guid><description>Data Integration We integrate sources and leads into all major crm services such as
HubSpot Sales Force Custom Solutions We also build crm custom solutions for teams requiring integration with .net workflows.</description></item><item><title>Data Warehousing and Management</title><link>https://justin-napolitano.github.io/products/data-warehouse/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 12:33:45 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://justin-napolitano.github.io/products/data-warehouse/</guid><description>Data Warehousing We integrate sales and lead data into scalable graph databases that permit massive scaling and easy integration into popular frameworks.
We specialize in:
JanusGraph Neo4j Data Management In order to secure data pipelines we build secure backends to ensure that data that data is never lost nor leaked.</description></item><item><title>Graph Database and Analysis</title><link>https://justin-napolitano.github.io/products/graph-data/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 12:33:45 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://justin-napolitano.github.io/products/graph-data/</guid><description>Graph Databases We integrate data into scalable graph databases models that permit massive scaling and easy integration into popular frameworks.
We specialize in:
JanusGraph Neo4j Graph Analysis Graph databases permit analysis of massive data sets within a single framework or simple data pipeline. We determine factors that contribute to successful sales.</description></item><item><title>Market Research</title><link>https://justin-napolitano.github.io/products/example/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 12:33:45 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://justin-napolitano.github.io/products/example/</guid><description>Rigorous market reports tailored to market sector.</description></item><item><title>Policy Research</title><link>https://justin-napolitano.github.io/products/policy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 12:33:45 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://justin-napolitano.github.io/products/policy/</guid><description>We research policy to ensure that products and services do not infringe upon consumer protection laws.</description></item><item><title>Sales Analysis and Forecasting</title><link>https://justin-napolitano.github.io/products/sales-forecsting/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 12:33:45 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://justin-napolitano.github.io/products/sales-forecsting/</guid><description>Sales Analysis We use Machine learning models to help us identify factors and patterns within data to better understand what really appeals to the market.
Sales Forecasting Meeting customer demand requires accurate sales forecasts to ensure that products are always available to customers. We build replicable models that we provide to our clients to ensure transparency.</description></item><item><title>The Importance of Empirical Analysis in Market Research</title><link>https://justin-napolitano.github.io/blog/empirical/empirical/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://justin-napolitano.github.io/blog/empirical/empirical/</guid><description>Empirical Analysis We focus on acquiring quality empirical data to prepare every report that we produce. Qualitative data and quantitive data must be verfied prior to including them in any project. Our data driven approach guarantees that our work is to the greatest extent possible free of bias and methodological errors.</description></item><item><title>The Importance of Rigor in Market Research</title><link>https://justin-napolitano.github.io/blog/rigor/rigor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://justin-napolitano.github.io/blog/rigor/rigor/</guid><description>Rigor Market Research reports are often manipulated to appeal to the bias of consumers. Rounding errors, large alphas, and closed source reports do not provide the rigor that analysis consumer deserve.
In our experience, technical reports detailing accurate results may not appeal to sales teams, founders, and executives that must justify their product to their board. We find that papers prepared according to the highest standards defined in the academic literature may not yield the results that consumers may expect.</description></item><item><title>The Importance of Transparency in Market Research</title><link>https://justin-napolitano.github.io/blog/transparency/transparency/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://justin-napolitano.github.io/blog/transparency/transparency/</guid><description>Transparency Black box models are the norm in the research industry. Some companies believe that their algorithms and pipelines are a product that must protected from the peering eyes of competitors. We take another aproach.
Napolitano-Tseng believes models should be documented and published in order for our clients to ensure that the work provided to them is produced according to the highest industry standards. When we are chosen to create reports, we include notebooks that document every part of our procedures to our customers.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://justin-napolitano.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://justin-napolitano.github.io/about/</guid><description>Napolitano-Tseng provides data driven market research to permit teams to focus on delivering their products to the market.
We provide the following services for sales teams:
Market Research Sales Analysis and Forecasting Policy Research We also offer:
CRM Development Data Warehousing and Management Graph Database and Analysis Cloud Infrastructre Development</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://justin-napolitano.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://justin-napolitano.github.io/contact/</guid><description>To contact us, please fill out the form below.</description></item></channel></rss>